prestigetime.com 2019-06-08

# PrestigeTime.com

Security and Privacy

Site Security

Our website and computer infrastructure are protected by state-of-the-art firewalls. All confidential information such as credit card numbers that are stored on our computers are encrypted at all times. All data communications through the PrestigeTime.com website are encrypted using a minimum of 128-bit SSL encryption with keys from COMODO. Once on our server we encrypt the information using 128-bit AES encryption.

Privacy

Personal Information

Your name, credit card information, shipping and billing addresses, telephone numbers, email address and all other private information will remain just that - private. Prestige Time uses your personal information for our billing, verification and shipping purposes only! 

Please note: We take online fraud seriously! If we receive a bogus order, we will notify and cooperate with the federal authorities. All information transmitted in the process of fraudulent orders will be turned over immediately to the FBI, and/or local police in your immediate area.

Prestige Time values your patronage and respects your privacy rights. Because we understand that you are concerned about your privacy, we have instituted policies intended to ensure that your personal information is handled safely and responsibly. As a policy, we do not sell, trade or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. 

Information Collection

Generally, you may browse our website without providing us with any personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, or credit card information. When you voluntarily submit your personally identifiable information to us by making a purchase from PrestigeTime.com, you are giving us your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information, and you understand and agree that we may share information about you and your transaction with other companies for the purpose of processing your transaction, including fraud prevention, vendor-direct shipping and credit card authorization. We may also disclose information when you tell us to do so, to identify or contact you, to protect your rights or the rights of PrestigeTime.com or as required by law. 

Electronic Communication

When you visit our website or communicate with us electronically by sending e-mails, you consent to receiving communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by e-mail or by posting notices on this Website. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing. 

Cookies and Data Collection Devices

In some instances, PrestigeTime.com may collect non-personal data through cookies, web logs, and other monitoring technologies. A cookie is an element of data that frequently contains an anonymous unique identifier. Such data is sent from the website to your browser, which may then store it on your system for future use. Our Website uses cookies to maintain information for your shopping cart and to facilitate your shopping experience so that you will not need to continually re-add items to your shopping cart during the same browser session.

Log Files

When you visit this Website, our web server automatically collects anonymous information such as log data and IP addresses. We may use the automatically collected information for a number of purposes, such as improving our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions.
